<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Roadmap on Apache Camel</title>
    <link>https://camel.apache.org/categories/Roadmap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Roadmap on Apache Camel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://camel.apache.org/categories/Roadmap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apache Camel 2020 Release Schedule</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2020/03/LTS-Release-Schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2020/03/LTS-Release-Schedule/</guid>
      <description>The Apache Camel project is moving to release schedule with Long Term Support (LTS) and non-LTS releases.
The plan is to have 2 yearly LTS releases and then non-LTS releases in between.
This allows the Camel project to innovate and move much faster in non-LTS releases.
And as well to offer production stable branches (LTS) where end users can stay on for a longer period of time and get CVEs and important/critical bug fixes only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camel 2019 in Numbers</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2019/12/2019-Numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2019/12/2019-Numbers/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the time of the year where we take a look back at 2019, and compile a brief summary of the Apache Camel project.
The big news of 2019 was the much anticipated release of Apache Camel 3.
Family of projects It was also in 2019 that the Camel project became a family of projects by introducing:
 Camel K Camel Quarkus  Making Apache Camel a trilogy. But it does not stop there; in early 2020 three will become five when we release:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Camel Kafka Connector: Introducing the latest project in the ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2019/12/Camel-Kafka-connector-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2019/12/Camel-Kafka-connector-intro/</guid>
      <description>The Apache Camel community introduces a new subproject in the ecosystem: Camel-Kafka-Connector. This project born as a PoC exploring the possibility of leveraging the Apache Camel components as Kafka source and sink connectors. The main idea behind the project is reusing the Camel Components&amp;rsquo; flexibility in a simple way, through a configuration file mixing Kafka Connect configuration and Camel route definitions and options.
What is Kafka Connect? It is an Apache Kafka&amp;rsquo;s framework that defines a standardized way to stream data in and out a kafka broker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Camel 3 is only 2 months away</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2019/10/Camel3-2monthsaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2019/10/Camel3-2monthsaway/</guid>
      <description>The Camel team is busy working on the last set of work for Apache Camel 3. Today the 2nd release candidate was built and published on a staging repository for early adopters to give it a try.
As I am busy myself then I just wanted to write a short blog post to keep the community posted that Apache Camel 3 is on the way, and that we expect it to be released by end of this year (sometime in November or December).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
