<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tooling on Apache Camel</title>
    <link>https://camel.apache.org/categories/Tooling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tooling on Apache Camel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://camel.apache.org/categories/Tooling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kamelet tooling support for Camel URI</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/05/KameletToolingSupportInCamelURI/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/05/KameletToolingSupportInCamelURI/</guid>
      <description>Kamelets (Kamel route snippets) are a new concept introduced in Camel K that allow users to connect to external systems via a simplified interface, hiding all the low level details about how those connections are implemented. There are several ways to consume them. One of them is as standard Camel Components. In this case, completion is provided to fill the template id and the parameter names. It is currently based on a fixed set of Kamelets provided by a snapshot of the kamelet catalog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Java debug a Camel K integration in VS Code - second iteration</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/05/JavaDebuggingInVSCode-iteration2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/05/JavaDebuggingInVSCode-iteration2/</guid>
      <description>Camel K is providing a new feature to Java debug deployed integrations. Before VS Code Tooling for Apache Camel K 0.0.25, more complex steps were required to leverage the VS Code Java debugging capabilities as explained in this previous blogpost.
I recorded a video which is following the steps in this blogpost.
Requirements  VS Code Extension Pack for Apache Camel with VS Code Tooling for Apache Camel K 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diagramming Camel routes with PlantUML</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/05/plantuml-diagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/05/plantuml-diagram/</guid>
      <description>Hello Camel riders!
I created a tool which allows to draw a PlantUML activity diagram from a running Camel context (not at design time).
The above image shows what kind of diagram you can expect.
I find it useful when I need to have a overall view of interactions between all the routes and endpoints, or to have a visual representation for better understanding and documentation.
You can find all the details on the public GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New release of VS Code Language Support for Apache Camel 0.0.32 and VS Code Tooling for Camel K 0.0.24</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/05/vscode-camel-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/05/vscode-camel-release/</guid>
      <description>A new release of VS Code Language Support for Apache Camel 0.0.32 is available. It includes upgrade of Camel catalogs, connected mode for Kafka topic completion and dependencies support for Camel K Java integration file.
Camel version upgrades The default Camel catalog has been upgraded from 3.8.0 to 3.9.0.
The Camel Quarkus catalog has been upgraded from 1.7.0 to 1.8.1.
The Camel Kafka Connector catalog has been upgraded from 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New release of VS Code Language Support for Apache Camel 0.0.31</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/03/VSCode-LanguageSupport-0.0.31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/03/VSCode-LanguageSupport-0.0.31/</guid>
      <description>A new release of VS Code Language Support for Apache Camel 0.0.31 is available. It includes upgrade of Camel catalogs and catalog runtime provider selection setting.
Camel Catalogs upgrades The default Camel catalog has been upgraded from 3.7.0 to 3.8.0.
The Camel Kafka Connector catalog has been upgraded from 0.7.0 to 0.8.0.
The Camel Quarkus catalog is provided with version 1.7.0.
Runtime provider setting Depending on the runtime used, the Camel components can have subtle differences, or even not be compatible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Java debug a Camel K integration in VS Code with Camel K 1.3.0</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/01/DebugInVSCodeWithCamelK1.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/01/DebugInVSCodeWithCamelK1.3.0/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON 17 May 2021: More recent related content available in this blogpost.
Camel K 1.3.0 is providing a new feature to Java debug deployed integrations. Even if Camel K 1.3.0 is not fully compatible with VS Code Tooling for Apache Camel K extension, it remains possible to leverage the VS Code Java debugging capabilities.
I recorded a video which is following the steps in this blogpost. I let you choose your preferred way to discover how to java debug your Camel K integration in VS Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New release of VS Code Language Support for Apache Camel 0.0.30</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/01/VSCode-LanguageSupport-0.0.30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2021/01/VSCode-LanguageSupport-0.0.30/</guid>
      <description>A new release of VS Code Language Support for Apache Camel 0.0.30 is available. It includes upgrade of Camel catalogs and Camel Kafka Connector related improvements.
Camel Catalogs upgrades The default Camel catalog has been upgraded from 3.6.0 to 3.7.0.
The Camel Kafka Connector catalog has been upgraded from 0.6.0 to 0.7.0.
Camel Kafka Connector related improvements Completion for Basic Configuration Some properties are not part of the Camel catalog material, neither of the Kafka Connect framework and applies to all Camel Kafka connectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New release of VS Code Language Support for Apache Camel 0.0.29</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2020/12/VSCode-LanguageSupport-0.0.29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2020/12/VSCode-LanguageSupport-0.0.29/</guid>
      <description>A new release of VS Code Language Support for Apache Camel 0.0.29 is available. It includes an interesting set of new features and two important bugfixes.
API based components support Camel has several API based components which are source code generated from external API. In 3.6.0, finer grained information is available through additional metadata (Camel catalog). This release is leveraging these metadata to propose improved completion, documentation and validation for these APU based components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New release of VS Code Language Support for Apache Camel 0.0.28</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2020/10/VSCode-LanguageSupport-0.0.28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2020/10/VSCode-LanguageSupport-0.0.28/</guid>
      <description>A new release of VS Code Language Support for Apache Camel 0.0.28 is available. It includes an interesting set of new features.
Camel 3.6.0 upgrade Camel 3.6.0 catalog is now provided by default. The 3.6.0 version is also leveraged internally.
Camel Kafka Connector Properties file improvements Previously, the support for Camel Kafka Connector was limited to Camel URI in camel.(sink|source).url property value. This release adds support for the list of properties provided for each parameter instead of using a potentially long Camel URI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Camel 3.0.0 with Windup</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2020/09/windup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2020/09/windup/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ll show you how Windup can help you plan and estimate your upgrade to Camel 3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language Support for Apache Camel - VS Code extension 0.0.20</title>
      <link>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2019/12/LanguageSupportTooling-0.0.20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camel.apache.org/blog/2019/12/LanguageSupportTooling-0.0.20/</guid>
      <description>During the past months, several noticeable new features have been added to improve the developer experience of application based on Apache Camel. These updates are available in the 0.0.20 release of Visual Studio (VS) Code extension.
Before going into the list of updates in detail, I want to note that I mentioned in the title the VS Code Extension release because VS Code extension is covering the broader set of new features.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
